ACTWU's Department of Occupational Safety and Health Records 5619/015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- OSHA Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust Transcript, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- OSHA Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust Transcript, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- OSHA Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust Transcript, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 11)
- OSHA Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust Transcript, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- OSHA Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust Transcript, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 13)
- OSHA Proposed Standard for Occupational Exposure to Cotton Dust Statement of the ACTWU, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 14)
- OSHA Proposed Standard for Occupational Exposure to Cotton Dust Statement of the ACTWU, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 15)
- OSHA Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust Transcript, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 16)
- OSHA Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust Transcript, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 17)
- OSHA Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust Transcript, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Contract Proposals, 1974-1975 (Box 79, Folder 19)
- Stevens Negotiations (EF Folder), 1974-176 (Box 79, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott Byssinosis, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott Activities, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 22)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott Clergy, 1977-1979 (Box 79, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott Clippings, 1976-1978 (Box 79, Folder 24)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott Community Activities, 1975-1979 (Box 79, Folder 25)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott Corporate Campaign, 1977-1980 (Box 79, Folder 26)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott Customers, 1974-1977 (Box 79, Folder 27)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott Discrimination, 1974-1979 (Box 80, Folder 27)
- J.P. Stevens Negotiations, 1976-1978 (Box 80, Folder 28)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Reports of Activities (Swaity), 1975-1979 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Law Violations (other than NLRA), 1973-1979 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Litigation, 1974-1978 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Elections, 1976-1979 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- J. P. Boycott Fair Measure, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- J. P. Stevens Field Reports, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott General, 1975-1979 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott ACTWU Highlights, 1977 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott International, 1973-1977 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Labels, 1975-1978 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Management Officers, 1975-1976 (Box 81, Folder 11)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Minutes - Staff Mfrs., 1976 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Miscellaneous, 1976-1979 (Box 81, Folder 13)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Negotiations, 1977-1979 (Box 81, Folder 14)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Management, 1975-1979 (Box 81, Folder 15)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Planning, 1974-1976 (Box 81, Folder 16)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Plants, 1976-1980 (Box 81, Folder 17)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Products, 1974-1976 (Box 81, Folder 18)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Publicity (Union Issued), 1975-1980 (Box 81, Folder 19)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Social Justice, 1976-1980 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Southerners for Economic Justice, 1976-1980 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Southern Studies, Institute for, 1975-1979 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Staff Manual, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Staff Meetings, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Stevens Organizer, 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Stevens Worker, 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Stockholders' Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Stockholders' Meetings, 1975-1978 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Taxes, 1974-1975 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Unfair Labor Practices. III, 1978-1980 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Unfair Labor Practices II, 1976-1977 (Box 82, Folder 12)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Unfair Labor Practices I, 1974-1975 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- J. P. Stevens Boycott U. S. Government Contracts (See Company Files) (Box 82, Folder 14)
  No Content
- Stevens Boycott Worksheets, 1963-1977 (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Fact Sheets J. P. Stevens and Company, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 82, Folder 16)
- J. P. Stevens 10-K Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 82, Folder 17)
- J. P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Supervisors' Personnel Manual Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina, 1974 (Box 82, Folder 18)
- J. P. Stevens and Company Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina Negotiations, 1974-1977 (Box 82, Folder 19)
- Interoffice Memos ACTWU Finley, Shemkmon, 1976-1977 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- ACTWU Inter-Office Memos, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- ACTWU Inter-Office Memos, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- ACTWU Inter-Office Memos, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- ACTWU Inter-Office Memos, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- ACTWI Inter-Office Memos, 1976-1977 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Liberty Leather Corp, 1983-1984 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Samuel Smidt Chemical Corp, 1979-1982 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Rohm and Haas Company, 1976-1982 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Tenneco Chemical, Inc., 1973 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Bay State Chemical Company, Inc., 1972 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Allied Chemical, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- BASF Wyandotte Corporation, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Yorkshire Chemicals Limited, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- J. P. Stevens Advisory Council, 1980-1981 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- J. P. Stevens Documents, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- ACTWU Worksheets, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Medical Survey Results, 1973-1978 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Monitor, Inc. and I. P. S., 1979 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- OSHA Recordkeeping, 1977-1979 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- Elmer Daughtrey, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 16)
- ACTWU Various Companies, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 17)
- OSH Case Ensign-Bickford, Inc. I Simsbury, Connecticut, 1979-1984 (Box 84, Folder 18)
- Badische, 1978-1982 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Air Contamination, 1979-1980 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Johnson and Johnson Expo and Medical Data, 1982-1983 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Johnson and Johnson, 1981-1983 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Johnson and Johnson ETO, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Johnson and Johnson Chromosome Study Reports ETO Docket Number H-200, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- OSHA Proposed Formaldehyde Standard, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- CHOH, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Proposed Formaldehyde Standard Testimony, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Formaldehyde in Workplace Study, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Formaldehyde Exposure, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- NCI, 1980-1986 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- CHOH NIOSH Study, Text, HHE, 1980-1986 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Formaldehyde Study, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- The Dyeing and Finishing of Textiles, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- The Dyeing and Finishing of Textiles, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- The Dyeing and Finishing of Textiles, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Occupational Formaldehyde Exposure, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- The Dyeing and Finishing of Textiles, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 13)
- The Dyeing and Finishing of Textiles, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 14)
- Challenges in the Practice of Occupational Medicine in The U. S., 1980 (Box 86, Folder 15)
- Occupational Medical Conference, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 16)
- Occupational Formaldehyde Exposure, 1986-1988 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- OSHA and EPA, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Formaldehyde Exposure, 1980-1988 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Formaldehyde Exposure, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Formaldehyde Exposure, 1985-1986 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Formaldehyde Exposure, 1974-1987 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Control of Occupational Exposures to Formaldehyde, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Formaldehyde, 1985-1987 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Imbus Testimony (Box 87, Folder 9)
- CHOH - NCI, 1980-1986 (Box 87, Folder 10)
- New York Times and CHOH (Box 87, Folder 11)
- CHOH - General, 1985-1986 (Box 87, Folder 12)
- OSHA Mortality Study, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 13)
- OSHA, 1972-1978 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Donovan v Hanes Knitwear, 1981-1984 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Hanes, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- OSH Hanes, 1981-1982 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Hanes Corporation Galax, Virginia, 1980-1981 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Hanes, 1981-1983 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Hanes, 1984 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Hanes, 1980-1982 (Box 88, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Hanes Workers Compensation, 1982-1983 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Hanes, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Upper Extremity Cumulative Trauma Disorders, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Upper Extremity Cumulative Trauma Disorders, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Upper Extremity Cumulative Trauma Disorders, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Hanes, 1982-1983 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Badische Corporation, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Hanes, 1980-1983 (Box 89, Folder 8)
- CD Study - Supreme Court Documents, 1980-1983 (Box 89, Folder 9)
- LOAS, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 10)
- Hanes General, 1982-1983 (Box 89, Folder 11)
- Chesebrough - Pond, 1983-1984 (Box 89, Folder 12)
- Hanes, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 13)
- OSH Case G. H. Bass and Company, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 14)
- J. P. Stevens Cases Labor Law Reform, 1976-1977 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- ACTWU Leadership Conference, Springfield, Virginia, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Textile Organizing Session, Silver Springs, Maryland, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Labor Law Reform Clippings, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Labor Law Reform ACTWU Cases - Clothing Division, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Labor Law Reform General, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Labor Law Reform ACTWU Testimony before Senate Committee, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Labor Law Reform, 1973-1977 (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Labor Law Reform ACTWU Testimony, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Toxic Substances Control I General, 1974-1980 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Toxic Substances Control Act, Administration, Carcinogens, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Toxic Substances "Toxic Substances Control Act-Section 8(e) Notices", 1979-1986 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Toxic Substance Control Act, Administration, Inventory, 1979-1982 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Toxic Substances Control Act II Administration, 1979-1987 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Toxic Substances Control Act II Administration, 1978-1985 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Toxic Substances Control II Administration of the Act, 1976-1978 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Toxic Substances Control Act Administration - Pre-Manufacture Notices, 1980-1985 (Box 91, Folder 8)
- Toxic Substances Control Clemson Seminar, 1974-1977 (Box 91, Folder 9)
- Toxic Substances Control House Committee on Government Operations, 1976 (Box 91, Folder 10)
- Toxic Substances Control Information Sources, 1975-1983 (Box 91, Folder 11)
- Toxic Substances Control International, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 12)
- Toxic Substances Control II Senate Subcommittee, 1975-1976 (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Toxic Substances Control III House Subcommittee, 1975-1976 (Box 91, Folder 14)
- Toxic Substance Control OECD, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 15)
- Toxic Substances Hazardous Wastes, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 16)
- Toxic Substances Textile Industry, 1979 (Box 91, Folder 17)
- Toxic Substance - TRI, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 18)
- Toxic Substances - TSC ACT - Existing Chemicals, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 19)
- Toxic Substances United Nations Environment Program, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 20)
- Toxic Substances Waste Dumping, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 21)
- The Toxic Substances Control Act of 1971, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 22)
- Vinyl Chloride I - General, 1974-1979 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Vinyl Chloride - II - IUD, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Vinyl Chloride - III- New York Academy of Science, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Vinyl Chloride IV - TWUA, 1974-1975 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Vinyl Chloride - V - U. S. - NIOSH, 1974-1975 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Vinyl Chloride - VI - U. S., 1974-1976 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Byssinosis Research Department File, 1977-1979 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Byssinosis Research Department File, 1977-1979 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Cotton Dust Appendices, 1975-1995 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Byssinosis Cotton Industry, 1979-1982 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Press Briefing, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Byssinosis Collective Bargaining Issues, 1970-1982 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Byssinosis Companies, Research Projects, etc., 1969-1980 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Educational Material I Byssinosis, 1978-1981 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Byssinosis Education Materials II OSHA Slide Show, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Byssinosis Egypt (Eric Frumin's Trip), 1982 (Box 93, Folder 9)
- Byssinosis - Foreign Countries other than United Kingdom, 1970-1976 (Box 93, Folder 10)
- Byssinosis - Hosiery Mills, 1980-1981 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- Byssinosis House Hearings, 1979-1981 (Box 93, Folder 12)
- Byssinosis International Standards, 1984 (Box 93, Folder 13)
- Byssinosis Knitting, 1981-1982 (Box 93, Folder 14)
- Byssinosis Knitting, 1982-1986 (Box 93, Folder 15)
- Byssinosis Literature - Pratt Study, 1980-1984 (Box 93, Folder 16)
- Byssinosis - Lawsuits, 1977-1980 (Box 93, Folder 17)
- Byssinosis Media Contacts, 1969-1984 (Box 93, Folder 18)
- Byssinosis National Academy of Science Study, 1978-1982 (Box 93, Folder 19)
- Byssinosis - Population at Risk Worksheet, 1967-1972 (Box 93, Folder 20)
- Byssinosis _ Proposals for Res., Ed., 1970-1974 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Byssinosis Sisal, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Byssinosis Spirometry, 1980-1985 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Byssinosis U. S. Government I-A - Agriculture Department, 1974-1979 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Byssinosis - U. S. Government II-A - NIOSH Criteria Doc., etc., 1971-1973 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Byssinosis U. S. Government II-B - NIOSH Criteria Doc. Etc., 1973-1978 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Byssinosis U. S. Government III - OSHA - General, 1971-1980 (Box 94, Folder 7)
- Byssinosis U. S. Government V OSHA, 1974-1975 (Box 94, Folder 8)
- Byssinosis U. S. Government VI-A OSHA, 1976-1977 (Box 94, Folder 9)
- Byssinosis U. S. Government VI-B OSHA, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 10)
- Byssinosis U. S. Government VII-A OSHA Proposed Standard, 1976-1978 (Box 94, Folder 11)
- Byssinosis U. S. Government VIII-C Proposed Standard, 1978-1979 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Byssinosis #1 U. S. Government VII-D Petition for Review by Circuit Court, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Byssinosis U. S. Government VII-D Petition for Review by Circuit Court, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Byssinosis #2 U. S. Government VII-D Petition for Review by Circuit Courts Continued, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Bysinosis VIII U. S. Government Supreme Court, 1980-1982 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Byssinosis VIII U. S. Government Supreme Court, 1980-1981 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Byssinosis VIII(A) Supreme Court (Briefs), 1980 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Byssinosis U. S. Government XI ANPR #2, 1982-1983 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Byssinosis U. S. Government XI ANPR #2, 1982-1983 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Byssinosis U. S. Government X ANPR #1, 1981-1982 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Byssinosis XIA ANPR #2 Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Byssinosis U. S. Government XIV Final Revision Circuit Court Petition, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Byssinosis Vertical Elutriator, 1979-1981 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Byssinosis Work Compensation Number II Responses Commissions, 1970-1972 (Box 96, Folder 6)
- Byssinosis Workers Compensation Number III Responses AFL-CIO, 1970-1971 (Box 96, Folder 7)
- Byssinosis Workmen's Compensation IV Burton Bill, 1970-1977 (Box 96, Folder 8)
- Byssinosis Workmen's Compensation V Burton's Bill Candidates' Responses, 1970 (Box 96, Folder 9)
- Byssinosis Workers Compensation Senate, 1983 (Box 96, Folder 10)
- Byssinosis Workmen's Compensation VI State Laws, 1971-1984 (Box 96, Folder 11)
- Byssinosis Workers Compensation VII Physicians, 1976-1978 (Box 96, Folder 12)
- Byssinosis W. C. IX Bills, 1977-1979 (Box 96, Folder 13)
- Byssinosis Workers Compensation House of Representatives, 1983 (Box 96, Folder 14)
- Workers Compensation House of Representatives, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 15)
- Byssinosis Workers' Compensation X House Hearings, 1979-1982 (Box 96, Folder 16)
- Byssinosis Remedies Other than Workers' Compensation XI, 1977-1979 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Byssinosis Yale University (Dr. Bouhuys other than literature), 1964-1983 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Yale University II Cotton Dust Bouhuys (Unpublished Writings), 1977-1980 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Cotton Dust ACTWU Activities (General), 1981-1983 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Cotton Dust Standard General, 1980-1983 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Cotton Dust Access to Info: Medical Monitor, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Cotton Dust Standard ATMI sub. II, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Cotton Dust Standard ATMI Sub., 1982-1983 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Cotton Dust ATMI Submissions, 1981-1982 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Cotton Dust Benefits of Standard, 1980 (Box 98, Folder 7)
- Cotton Dust Standard Congressional Hearings, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Cotton Dust Standard Cost-Benefit Analysis (Levenstein and Frumin), 1982 (Box 98, Folder 9)
- Cotton Dust Control, 1980 (Box 98, Folder 10)
- Cotton Dust Enforcement, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 11)
- Cotton Dust Standard Economic Impact II: General Worksheets, 1978-1982 (Box 98, Folder 12)
- Cotton Dust Standard Economic Impact III - Analysis (Box 98, Folder 13)
- Cotton Dust Standard Economic Impact I: Co. Worksheets, 1978-1980 (Box 98, Folder 14)
- Cotton Dust Fact Sheets, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 15)
- Cotton Dust Hughes: Disability, 1979-1980 (Box 98, Folder 16)
- Cotton Dust Standard Literature Reviews Notes, 1973-1975 (Box 98, Folder 17)
- Cotton Dust Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 98, Folder 18)
- Cotton Dust Mortality Studies, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 19)
- Cotton Dust NAS Comm. Rep., 1980-1982 (Box 98, Folder 20)
- Cotton Dust Legal Advice and Prep, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 21)
- Cotton Dust Standard Morral's Analysis of C/B (Box 98, Folder 22)
- Cotton Dust Standard OMB Review of OSHA Proposal, 1978-1983 (Box 98, Folder 23)
- Cotton Dust Standard OSHA Compliance Programming, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 24)
- Cotton Dust Respirators, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 25)
- Cotton Dust Standard Science Mag. Letters, 1983 (Box 98, Folder 26)
- Cotton Dust Scientific Review of Byssinosis Conference, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 27)
- Cotton Dust Supreme Court, 1980 (Box 98, Folder 28)
- Cotton Dust Standard Technology General, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 29)
- Cotton Dust Standard Technology's Role in Compliance (Ruttenburg), 1982 (Box 98, Folder 30)
- Cotton Dust U. S. House Committee Hearing, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 31)
- Cotton Dust U. S. III Court Decisions, 1979 (Box 98, Folder 32)
- Cotton Dust US IV Standard, 1976-1978 (Box 98, Folder 33)
- Cotton Dust U. S. Department of Labor Representative to Congress, 1979 (Box 98, Folder 34)
- Cotton Dust Washed Cotton Studies, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 35)
- Opportunities and Strategies for U. S. Textile, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 36)
- Cotton Dust Standards Post-Hearing Statement ACTWU, 1980 (Box 98, Folder 37)
- Cotton Dust Standards Hearings I General, 1983 (Box 98, Folder 38)
- Cotton Dust Standards Hearings II Testimony, 1983 (Box 98, Folder 39)
- Cotton Dust Hearings III Notes, Worksheets, 1983 (Box 98, Folder 40)
- Cotton Dust Standard Hearing IV Post-Hearing Subm., 1983 (Box 98, Folder 41)
- Cotton Dust Standards Hearing V: Economic Impact, 1983 (Box 98, Folder 42)
- Cotton Dust Standards hearing VI Single-Shift Monitor, 1982-1983 (Box 98, Folder 43)
- ACTWU Activities George Perkel Consultant, 1980-1982 (Box 98, Folder 44)
- ACTWU General, 1976-1981 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- General AFL-CIO, 1970-1981 (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Asbestos, 1979-1982 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- GP General Barkin, Sol, 1979-1981 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Bibliographies, 1980 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Brookings Conference Scientific Basis for Health and Safety Regulations, 1979-1981 (Box 99, Folder 6)
- GP General Burlington Cotton Dust I, 1978-1980 (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Burlington - Joint Research, 1981-1982 (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Burlington Cotton Dust II Weill's Study, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Carpal Tunnel Syndrome, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 10)
- GP General Collective Bargaining, 1981-1982 (Box 99, Folder 11)
- Cost-Benefit Analysis General, 1979-1982 (Box 99, Folder 12)
- Cost Benefit Analysis, 1980-1981 (Box 99, Folder 13)
- Costs of Illness, 1975-1980 (Box 99, Folder 14)
- Cost-Benefit Analysis Regulatory Impact Analysis Seminar, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 15)
- Disability Occupational Characteristics, 1969-1980 (Box 99, Folder 16)
- DOSH Staff Mtg., 1980-1981 (Box 99, Folder 17)
- Dyers Mortality, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 18)
- GP General Education Materials on Labor, 1976-1978 (Box 99, Folder 19)
- GP Formaldehyde General, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 20)
- Life, Value of, 1980-1990 (Box 99, Folder 21)
- GP General MacNeil Lehrer Show, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 22)
- McGraw-Hill Surveys, 1980 (Box 99, Folder 23)
- ACTWU Health and Safety Local Union Action Manual (Box 99, Folder 24)
- Manuals (Box 99, Folder 24)
- Management and Ethics, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 25)
- GP General Mount Sinai, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 26)
- GP General NIOSH General, 1979-1981 (Box 99, Folder 27)
- GP General NIOSH Control Technology Cotton, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 28)
- GP General NIOSH Cotton Textiles Mortality Study, 1975-1977 (Box 99, Folder 29)
- GP General NIOSH Dye Control Technology, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 30)
- GP General NIOSH Pulmonary Function Study, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 31)
- NOISE, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 32)
- Occupational Medicine, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 33)
- OSHA - Cancer Policy, 1980 (Box 99, Folder 34)
- GP General OSHA Films, Audio Visual, 1970-1978 (Box 99, Folder 35)
- Personal: Article in Chest, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 36)
- Respiratory Diseases: Prevalence, 1980 (Box 99, Folder 37)
- GP General Rowan, Richard L., 1978 (Box 99, Folder 38)
- Statistical Methods - Significant Differences, 1983 (Box 99, Folder 38)
- GP General S.T.A.R., 1981 (Box 99, Folder 39)
- GP General Sheinkman, 1977-1979 (Box 99, Folder 40)
- Staff Training Inst. (Organizers), 1978 (Box 99, Folder 41)
- Staff Management (Southern), 1979 (Box 99, Folder 42)
- Staff Meetings (DOSH), 1979-1980 (Box 99, Folder 43)
- Stetin - Speech Notes, 1979-1980 (Box 99, Folder 44)
- GP General Stetin, 1972-1979 (Box 99, Folder 45)
- GP General TWUA Merger with ACW, 1976-1978 (Box 99, Folder 46)
- GP General Textile Division, ACTWU, 1976-1978 (Box 99, Folder 47)
- Workers Compensation General, 1981-1983 (Box 99, Folder 48)
- Workers Compensation Cotton Dust, 1978-1981 (Box 99, Folder 49)
- AFL-CIO v Ray Marshall, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Cotton Dust Standard, 1981 (Box 100, Folder 2)
- Cotton Dust Standard ACTWU, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 3)
- Cotton Dust Conference, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Cotton Dust Control Manual, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 5)
- Cotton Dust ACTWU History, 1981 (Box 100, Folder 6)
- Cotton Dust Standards Volume I of Union Statement, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 7)
- Cotton Dust Standard Introductory Statement by Sol Stetin, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 8)
- Cotton Dust Standard Volume I of Union Statement, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 9)
- Cotton Dust Standard Post-Hearing Statement, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 10)
- GP Cotton Dust ACTWU Pre-Standard Hearing, 1975-1977 (Box 100, Folder 11)
- GP Cotton Dust ACTWU: Post-Hearing Activities I Economic Advantages Interference, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 12)
- GP Cotton Dust ACTWU: Post-Hearing Activities II, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 13)
- GP Cotton Dust Afifi, E.M., 1976-1977 (Box 100, Folder 14)
- GP Cotton Dust ATMI - Post Hearing, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 16)
- Cotton Dust Standard Appeals Committee Decision, 1979 (Box 100, Folder 17)
- Cotton Dust Standard Appeal to CCA, 1978-1979 (Box 100, Folder 18)
- Cotton Dust Standard Supreme Court Appeal, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 19)
- Beck, G.J., Prospective Study of Chronic Lung Disease in CTW, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 20)
- GP Cotton Dust Byssinosis - Selected Materials, 1970-1978 (Box 100, Folder 21)
- GP Cotton Dust Bouhuys I, 1977-1978 (Box 100, Folder 22)
- GP Cotton Dust Burgess, Wm. A, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 23)
- GP Cotton Dust Burlington Industries, 1971-1977 (Box 100, Folder 24)
- Cotton Dust Contract Proposals, 1979 (Box 100, Folder 25)
- GP Cotton Dust CDS - Educational Materials, 1978-1979 (Box 100, Folder 26)